dogomania.com 2002-06-03

# Dog-O-Mania - The biggest dogs related search engine & resource: Privacy policy

**Main menu:**  
\- [Feedback](http://www.dogomania.com/contact.shtml)  
\- [Advertising](http://www.dogomania.com/advertising.shtml)  
\- [Privacy policy](http://www.dogomania.com/privacy.shtml)  
\- [Survey](http://38.148.250.3/cgi-win/client.exe?readers,welcome,ad5378a,1001)  
\- [News](http://www.dogomania.com/news/)  
\- [Newsletter](http://www.dogomania.com/newsletter.shtml)  
\- [Awards](http://www.dogomania.com/awards/awards.shtml)

**Breeds:**  
\- [Breeds](http://www2.dogomania.com/breed/)  
\- [Breeders](http://www2.dogomania.com/gallery/breeders/) New!  
\- [Gallery](http://www2.dogomania.com/gallery/breeds/) New!  
\- [Standards](http://www2.dogomania.com/gallery/standards/)  

**Names:**  
\- [25000 dog names](http://www.dogomania.com/dog_names.shtml)  
\- [Submit a name](http://www.dogomania.com/addname.shtml)

**Shows:**  
\- [Search](http://www.dogomania.com/shows.shtml)  
\- [Add a dog show](http://www.dogomania.com/addshow.shtml)  
\- [Kennel clubs](http://www.dogomania.com/kennels.shtml)  
\- [Entry forms](http://www.dogomania.com/entry_forms.shtml)  
\- [Titles](http://www.dogomania.com/titles.shtml)

**Discussions:**  
\- [Read forum](http://www.dogomania.com/forum/index.php)  
\- [New topic](http://www.dogomania.com/forum/posting.php?mode=newtopic&f=1)  
\- [Search](http://www.dogomania.com/forum/search.php)

**Resources:**  
\- [Fun](http://www.dogomania.com/fun.shtml)  
\- [Stories](http://www.dogomania.com/stories.shtml)  
\- [Poetry](http://www.dogomania.com/poetry.shtml)  
\- [Art](http://www.dogomania.com/art.shtml)  
\- [Graphics](http://www.dogomania.com/webgraphics.shtml)  
\- [Windows themes](http://www.dogomania.com/winthemes.shtml)  
\- [Screen savers](http://www.dogomania.com/screensavers.shtml)  
\- [Software](http://www.dogomania.com/download.shtml)

**Top 100:**  
\- [Visit Top Sites](http://www.dogomania.com/topsites/)  
\- [Sign up!](http://www.dogomania.com/signup.shtml)  
\- [Members login](http://www.dogomania.com/login.shtml)

**Rescues:**  
\- [Shelters](http://www.dogomania.com/shelters.shtml)  
\- [Available](http://www.dogomania.com/dogs_in_need/search.php?Category=1&main=yes) New!  
\- [Wanted](http://www.dogomania.com/dogs_in_need/search.php?Category=2&main=yes) New!  
\- [Lost](http://www.dogomania.com/dogs_in_need/search.php?Category=3&main=yes) New!  
\- [Found](http://www.dogomania.com/dogs_in_need/search.php?Category=4&main=yes) New!  
\- [Submit info](http://www.dogomania.com/addrdog.php)

**Online Shops:**  
\- [Free classified ads](http://www.dogomania.com/ads.shtml)  
\- [Books](http://www.dogomania.com/category/Books/)  
\- [Videos](http://www.dogomania.com/category/Books/Video)  
\- [Reflectors for dogs](http://www.dogomania.com/shop/shop-col.shtml)  
\- [Dog toys](http://www.dogomania.com/shop/toys.shtml)

**Webmasters:**  
\- [Add your page](http://www.dogomania.com/addurl.shtml)  
\- [Add picture](http://www.dogomania.com/addphoto.shtml)  
\- [Press](http://www.dogomania.com/addpress.shtml)  
\- [Search box](http://www.dogomania.com/searchbox.shtml)  
\- [Link to us](http://www.dogomania.com/banners.shtml)  
\- [Free homepages](http://www.dogomania.com/home/signup.shtml)  
\- [Free mini sites](http://www.dogomania.com/addbreeder.shtml)  
\- [Free Email](http://mail.dogomania.com/)  
\- [Free Topsites list](http://www.m4d.com/cgi-bin/signup.pl)  
\- [Free WebBoard](http://www.m4d.com/cgi-bin/signup.pl)

| 

**Privacy Statement for Dog-O-Mania:**

M4D.COM has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Dog-O-Mania. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **Dog-O-Mania** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Children's Guidelines

This site gives children the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to [dogs@m4d.com](mailto:dogs@m4d.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You can send email to [dogs@m4d.com](mailto:dogs@m4d.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  Margo Peron  
Dog-O-Mania M4D.COM [dogs@m4d.com](http://www.dogomania.com/contact.shtml)
